Inventaris van het archief van het Ministerie van Economische Zaken: Directoraat-Generaal voor de Buitenlandse Economische Betrekkingen (vergaderstukken van internationale organisaties), 1945-1967
Nationaal Archief, Den Haag
- UNITED NATIONS CONFERENCE ON TRADE AND DEVELOPMENT (UNCTAD).
  - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development., 1964; 1823
    E/Conf. 46 nr. 32 - 39
  - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development., 1964; 1824
    E/Conf. 46 nr. 40 - 57
  - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development., 1964; 1825
    E/Conf. 46 nr. 58 - 70
  - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development., 1964; 1826
    E/Conf. 46 nr. 71 - 74
  - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development., 1964; 1827
    E/Conf. 46 nr. 75 - 83
  - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development., 1964; 1828
    E/Conf. 46 nr. 84 - 130
  - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development., 1964; 1829
    E/Conf. 46 nr. 131 - 140
  - Diverse Stukken., 1830
    - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development, 1964
      E/Conf. 46 CI
    - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development, 1964
      E/Conf. 46 CI/L nr. 1 -57
    - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development, 1964
      E/Conf. 46 CI/REC nr. 1-' 9
    - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development, 1964
      E/Conf. 46 CI/WP 2
  - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development., 1964; 1831
    E/Conf. 46 CI/SR nr. 1 - 70
  - Diverse Stukken., 1832
    - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development, 1964
      E/Conf. 46 C 2
    - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development, 1964
      E/Conf. 46 C 2/L nr. 1 - 54
    - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development, 1964
      E/Conf. 46 C 2/REC
  - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development., 1964; 1833
    E/Conf. 46 C 2/SR nr. 1 - 62
  - Diverse Stukken., 1834
    - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development, 1964
      E/Conf. 46 C 3
    - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development, 1964
      E/Conf. 46 C 3/L nr. 1 - 95
  - Diverse Stukken., 1835
    - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development, 1964
      E/Conf. 46 C 3/REC
    - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development, 1964
      E/Conf. 46 C 3/SR nr. 1 - 35
  - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development., 1964; 1836
    E/Conf. 46 C 3/SR nr. 36 - 64
  - Diverse Stukken., 1837
    - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development, 1964
      E/Conf. 46 C 4
    - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development, 1964
      E/Conf. 46 C 4/L nr. 1 - 27
    - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development, 1964
      E/Conf. 46 C 4/REC
    - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development, 1964
      E/Conf. 46 C 4/SR nr. 1 - 41
  - Diverse Stukken., 1838
    - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development, 1964
      E/Conf. 46 C 5
    - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development, 1964
      E/Conf. 46 C 5/L nr. 1 - 28
    - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development, 1964
      E/Conf. 46 C 5/REC
  - Diverse Stukken., 1839
    - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development, 1964
      E/Conf. 46 C 5/SC 1/L
    - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development, 1964
      E/Conf. 46 C 5/SC 1/SR
    - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development, 1964
      E/Conf. 46 C 5/SR 1 - 42
  - Diverse Stukken., 1840
    - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development, 1964
      E/Conf. 46 C 6/L
    - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development, 1964
      E/Conf. 46 NGO
    - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development, 1964
      E/Conf. 46 cred/SR
    - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development, 1964
      E/Conf. 46 bur/SR
    - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development, 1964
      E/Conf. 46 journal
  - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development., 1964; 1841
    A/C 2/L
  - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development., 1964; 1842
    E/Conf. 46/L nr. 1 - 27
  - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development., 1964; 1843
    E/Conf. 46/L nr. 28 + add.
  - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development., 1964; 1844
    E/Conf. 46/P nr. 1 - 13
  - Diverse Stukken., 1845
    - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development. 1964
      E/Conf. 46/PC conf. room paper nr. 1 - 10
    - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development. 1964
      E/Conf. 46/PC nr. 1 - 55
  - Diverse Stukken., 1846
    - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development, 1964
      E/Conf. 46/PC/L nr. 1 - 30
    - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development, 1964
      E/Conf. 46/PC/SC1, SC2, SC3, SC4
  - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development., 1964; 1847
    E/Conf. 46/SC 1/SR, SC2/SR, SC3/SR, SC4/SR, SC5/SR
  - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development., 1964; 1848
    E/Conf. 46 PC/SR
  - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development., 1964; 1849
    E/Conf. 46 SR nr. 1 - 36
  - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development., 1964; 1850
    E/Conf. 46 STA nr. 1 - 50
  - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development., 1964; 1851
    E/Conf. 46 STA nr. 51 - 85
  - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development., 1964; 1852
    E/Conf. 46 STA nr. 86 - 162
  - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development., 1964; 1853
    E/C 5 + E/CN
  - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development., 1964; 1854
    CTD. A.B.C.D.E. + M
  - Diverse Stukken., 1855
    - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development, 1964
      CTD. alg.
    - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development, 1964
      CTD. review
    - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development, 1964
      CTD. SP
    - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development, 1964
      CTD. BIO
  - Diverse Stukken., 1856
    - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development, 1964
      Final Act and Report
    - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development, 1964
      Policy Statements
    - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development, 1964
      Commodity Trade
  - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development., 1964; 1857
    Diversen
  - Diverse Stukken., 2199
    - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development, 1965
      TAD Board Comm. III
    - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development, 1965
      TAB Board Subcomm. III
- UNITED NATIONS DEVELOPMENT PROGRAMME (UNDP).
  In 1965 ontstaan door samenvoeging van het EPTA (1949) en het UNSF (1958).
  - Diverse Stukken., 1884
    - United Nations Special Fund, 1965
      SF/INF
    - United Nations Special Fund, 1963-1965
      SF/L
    - United Nations Special Fund, 1964
      SF/R
    - United Nations Special Fund, 1965
      SF/SR
  - Diverse Stukken., 1880
    - United Nations Development programme, 1965
      DP/L1
    - United Nations Development programme, 1965
      DP/L2
    - United Nations Development programme, 1965
      DP/SF/R1
- UN/ECONOMIC AND SOCIAL COUNCIL (ECOSOC).
  ECOSOC is een van de hoofdorganen van de Verenigde Naties.
  - Stukken Verenigde Naties., 1949; 922
    Economic and Social Council
  - Diverse Stukken., 1880
    - Economic and social council, 1964
      E/C5
    - Economic and social council, 1964
      E/C5/INF
    - Economic and social council, 1964
      E/C5/L
    - Economic and social council, 1964
      E/C5/SR
  - Diverse Stukken., 1881
    - Economic and social council, 1964
      E/C5/WGL
    - Economic and social council, 1964
      E/C5/WG2
    - Economic and social council, 1964
      E/Conf.
    - Economic and social council, 1964
      E/Conf. 32/CI/SR 1 - 8
    - Economic and social council, 1960
      E/Conf. 32/C2/SR 1 - 20
    - Economic and social council, 1960
      E/Conf. 32/EX/SR 1 - 11
    - Economic and social council, 1955-1963
      E/ECE
  - Diverse Stukken., 1882
    - Economic and social council, 1962-1963
      E/ECE/Coal
    - Economic and social council, 1955-1962
      E/ECE/Steel
    - Economic and social council, 1961-1963
      E/ECE/Tim
    - Economic and social council, 1964
      E/ICEF
- UN/ECONOMIC COMMISSION FOR EUROPE (ECE).
  In 1947 ingestelde economische regionale commissie van de Verenigde Naties, ter vergroting van de economische activiteiten en stimulering van de economische betrekkingen van de landen binnen de regio met de buitenwereld.
  - Economische samenwerking West-Europa., 2302
    330.2 (4-15) Council stukken
  - Economische Commissie voor Europa., 1950-1952; 2303
    330.2 (4E.) C.E. Transport Division
  - Diverse Stukken., 2306
    - Economische samenwerking West-Europa E.C.A, 1950-1951
      330.19(5-15)
    - Intra European Payments Committee, 1949
      330.19(4-15)
  - Economie Commission for Europe., 1954-1955; 797
    Inland Transport Committee
  - Economie Commission for Europe., 1955-1956; 798
  - Diverse Stukken., 848
    - Diverse Stukken Ver. Naties, 1949-1950
      E/ECE/IM 38-E/ECE/EM 48
    - Diverse Stukken Ver. Naties, 1949-1950
  - Diverse Stukken., 849
    - Diverse Stukken Ver. Naties, 1950-1952
      IM/19-IM/36
    - Diverse Stukken Ver. Naties, 1950-1954
      IM/WP
  - Economie Commission for Europe., mei 1949 - okt. 1958; 967
    o.a. Verslagen
  - Diverse Stukken., 1072
    - Economie Commission for Europe (Vergaderingen te Genève), 1955
      Nederland-Albanië, Nederland-Oost-Duitsland, Nederland-Polen, Nederland-USSR
    - Economie Commission for Europe (Vergaderingen te Genève), 1956
      Algemene-, financiële-, en officiële stukken
  - Economie Commission for Europe (Vergaderingen te Genève)., 1956; 1073
    Polen, Roemenië, Tsjechoslowakije, USSR
  - Economie Commission for Europe (Vergaderingen te Genève)., 1958; 1074
    Algemene en officiële stukken, Albanië, Hongarije
  - Diverse Stukken., 1876
    - Economie Commission for Europe, 1962-1963
      Coal
    - Economie Commission for Europe, 1958-1963
      Coal./Doc. de travail working paper
    - Economie Commission for Europe, 1963
      Coal./Doc. de Séance
  - Diverse Stukken., 1877
    - Economie Commission for Europe, 1960
      Coal./CSWP/working paper
    - Economie Commission for Europe, 1963
      Coal./CTSC
    - Economie Commission for Europe, 1962-1963
      Coal./CTSC/working paper
  - Diverse Stukken., 1878
    - Economie Commission for Europe, 1962-1963
      Coal./P
    - Economie Commission for Europe, 1961-1963
      Coal./P/working paper
    - Economie Commission for Europe, 1963
      Coal./prod.
  - Diverse Stukken., 1879
    - Economie Commission for Europe, 1962-1963
      Coal./prod./working paper
    - Economie Commission for Europe, 1962
      Coal./UWP/
    - Economie Commission for Europe, 1962-1963
      Coal./UWP/working paper
    - Economie Commission for Europe, 1962
      Coal./UWP/AC/working paper
  - Diverse Stukken., 1882
    - Economie Commission for Europe, 1963
      ECE/XVIII/D.rep.
    - Economie Commission for Europe, 1963
      ECE/IXVIII/L
    - Economie Commission for Europe, 1963
      ECE/XVIII/SR
  - Diverse Stukken., 1883
    - Economie Commission for Europe, 1964
      FAO/ECE/Log
    - Economie Commission for Europe, 1964
      FAO/ECE/Log/lnformation paper
    - Economie Commission for Europe, 1962-1963
      FAO/ECE/Stats
    - Economie Commission for Europe, 1964
      FAO/ECE/Stats - Fo
    - European Office, 1963
      FAO/EFC rapport
    - Food and Agriculture Organization, 1963
      FAO/EFC-63 conf. room doc.
  - Diverse Stukken., 1885
    - Economie Commission for Europe, 1962
      ST/ECE/Coal.
    - Economie Commission for Europe, 1963
      ST/ECE/Energy
    - Economie Commission for Europe, 1962
      ST/ECE/Steel
    - Economie Commission for Europe, 1960-1963
      Steel
  - Diverse Stukken., 1886
    - Economie Commission for Europe, 1955-1963
      Steel/Working paper
    - Economie Commission for Europe, 1960-1963
      Steel/WP2
    - Economie Commission for Europe, 1960-1963
      Steel/WP3
    - Economie Commission for Europe, 1963
      Steel/WP3/Working paper
  - Diverse Stukken., 1887
    - Economie Commission for Europe, 1962
      Tim/
    - Economie Commission for Europe, 1962
      Tim/Board
    - Economie Commission for Europe, 1963
      Tim/Conf. room doc.
    - Economie Commission for Europe, 1959-1963
      Tim/Working paper 24-73
  - Diverse Stukken., 1888
    - Economie Commission for Europe, 1963
      Tim/Working paper 74-75
    - Economie Commission for Europe, 1964
      Tim/SAW/
    - Economie Commission for Europe, 1960
      Tim/WP1/
  - The European Gas Economy., 1962; 1896
    ST/ECE/Gas/4
  - Diverse Stukken., 1924
    - Netherlands expert engineering consultation, 1949
    - Diverse Stukken, 1950
      IM/Document de travail 6-24
  - PRELIMINARY REPORT OF THE TEMPORARY SUB-COMMISSION ON ECONOMIC RECONSTRUCTION OF DEVASTATED AREAS., 1946; 364
  - ECONOMIC AND SOCIAL COUNCIL E/ECE/SR1., 1947; 365
  - ECONOMIC AND SOCIAL COUNCIL E/ECE/DEL/DOC/W., 1947; 365
  - ECONOMIC AND SOCIAL COUNCIL E/ECE/C1/SR., 1947; 365
  - ECONOMIC AND SOCIAL COUNCIL E/ECE/C11/SR., 1947; 365
  - ECONOMIC AND SOCIAL COUNCIL E/ECE/SR2/1-18., 1947; 365
  - ECONOMIC AND SOCIAL COUNCIL E/ECE/SR3/1-19., 1948; 365
  - ECONOMIC AND SOCIAL COUNCIL E/ECE/SR4/1-25., 1949; 365
  - ECONOMIC AND SOCIAL COUNCIL E/ECE/SR5/1-25., 1950; 366
  - ECONOMIC AND SOCIAL COUNCIL E/ECE/SR6/1-27., 1951; 366
  - ECONOMIC AND SOCIAL COUNCIL E/ECE/SR7/1-25 EN. ECE/7 WORKING PAPERS 1-23., 1952; 367
  - ECONOMIC AND SOCIAL COUNCIL E/ECE/SR8/1-25., 1953; 367
  - ECONOMIC AND SOCIAL COUNCIL E/ECE/SR9/1-28. ECE/9/WORKING PAPER 1-20., 1954; 368
  - ECONOMIC AND SOCIAL COUNCIL E/ECE/1-82., 1947-1948; 368
  - ECONOMIC AND SOCIAL COUNCIL E/ECE/83-142., 1949-1952; 369
  - ECONOMIC AND SOCIAL COUNCIL E/ECE/142-192., 1952-1954; 370
  - ECE MONTHLY BULLETIN., 1948-1954; 371
  - ECONOMIC COMMISSION FOR EUROPE E/ECE/204-258., 1955; 372
  - ECE MONTHLY BULLETIN., 1955-1957; 373
  - INDUSTRY AND MATERlALS COMMITTEE. HOUSING SUB. COMMITTEE., 1952-1954; 374
  - HOUSING COMMITTEE., 1955-1957; 374
  - TIMBER COMMITTEE., 1955-1957; 375
  - INLANDS TRANSPORT COMMITTEE W/TRANS/WP6/84-93., 1957; 376
  - W/TRANS/WP11/57-76., 1956-1957; 376
  - W/TRANS/WP/14/42-70., 1955-1957; 376
  - W/TRANS/WP15/34-43., 1957; 376
  - W/TRANS/WP15/44-48., 1957; 376
  - W/TRANS/WP20/57-77., 1956-1957; 376
  - WIT/RANS/184-203., 1956-1957; 377
  - W/TRANS/WP11/129-135., 1956-1957; 377
  - W/TRANS/WP14/62-76., 1955-1957; 377
  - W/TRANS/WP15/48-55., 1956-1957; 377
  - W/TRANS/WP24/24-41., 1955-1956; 377
  - W/TRANS/WP28/13-43., 1955-1956; 377
  - W/TRANS/WP29/15-36., 1956-1957; 377
  - W/TRANS/WP30/58-65., 1957; 377
  - W/TRANS/WP30/67-86., 1957; 377
  - W/TRANS/WP32/1-8., 1955-1957; 377
  - COAL/CTSC/WORKING PAPERS no. 1-17., 1956; 378
  - COAL/CTSC/WORKING PAPERS no.18-33., 1957; 378
  - W/COAL/CTSC/64-74., 1954-1955; 378
  - COAL/CTSC/91-108., 1955-1956; 378
  - COAL/CTSC/109-121., 1957-1958; 378
  - COAL COMMITTE E/ECE/COAL/UWP/40,59-76., 1955-1956; 379
  - E/ECE/IM/WP5/7-15. E/ECE/CTSC/38-56., 1953-1955; 379
  - W/COAL/CTSC/74-82., 1955; 379
  - COAL/CWSP/12-16., 1953-1955; 379
  - E/ECE/COAL/SR22-26., 1952; 379
  - COAL/UWP/WORKING PAPER no.10-22., 1956-1957; 379
  - COAL/94-108., 1955-1957; 379
  - COAL/109-116., 1957; 379
  - E/ECE/COAL/96-128., 1954-1958; 379
  - COAL COMMITTEE / MONTHLY COAL STATISTICAL SUMMARY., 1955; 380
  - COAL/WORKING PAPER no.1-4., 1956; 380
  - COAL/WORKING PAPER no.5-19., 1956; 380
  - COAL/WORKING PAPER no. 10-31., 1957; 380
  - W/COAL/no.35-47., 1954-1955; 380
  - COAL/CWP/96-118., 1954-1955; 380
  - COAL COMMITTE., 1956-1957; 381
  - CONFERENCE OF EUROPEAN STATISTICIANS., STATISTICAL COMMISSION 34-61.; 1955-1956; 381
  - CONF/EUR./STATS/22-80., 1957; 381
  - CONF/EUR./STATS/WG3/26-44., 1956; 381
  - CONF/EUR./STATS/WP5., 1955; 381
  - CONF/EUR./STATS/21-33., 1955; 381
  - CONF/EUR./STATS/WP4/2-11., 1955-1956; 382
  - CONF/EUR./STATS/WP5/10.1-16., 1955; 382
  - CONF/EUR./STATS/WP6/1-25., 1955-1956; 382
  - CONF/EUR./STATS/WP6/26-52., 1957; 382
  - CONF/EUR./STATS/WP6/E.G.2-30., 1955-1956; 382
  - CONF/EUR./STATS/WP7/1-37., 1956-1957; 383
  - CONF/EUR./STATS/WP9/1-9., 1956-1957; 383
  - CONF/EUR./STATS/WP10/1-22., 1957; 383
  - CONF/EUR./STATS/WP11/1-18., 1957; 383
  - E/ECE/193-203., 1955; 384
  - E/ECE/225-244., 1956; 384
  - E/ECE/264-270., 1957; 384
  - E/ECE/271-287., 1957; 384
  - E/ECE/291., 1947-1957; 384
  - E/ECE/263-310., 1955-1958; 385
  - E/ECE/311 -330., 1958; 385
  - E/ECE/333-363., 1959; 385
  - E/ECE/INF/1-30., 1947; 386
  - E/ECE/INF/31-63., 1947-1948; 386
  - Trade/6-31., 1954-1955; 387
  - Trade/32-50., 1955-1956; 387
  - ECE/10//WORKING PAPER 1-11., 1955; 388
  - E/ECE/SR.10/1-10 TENTH SESSION., 1955; 388
  - E/ECE/SR.10/11-21TENTH SESSION., 1955; 388
  - E/ECE/SR.11/1-11 ELEVENTH SESSION., 1956; 388
  - E/ECE/SR.11/12-23 ELEVENTH SESSION., 1957; 388
  - E/ECE/SR.11 CONF. ROOM Doc. 1-4., 1956; 388
  - E/ECE/SR. 11 CONF. Doc. 4-23., 1956; 389
  - E/ECE/SR.12/1-12 TWELFTH SESSION., 1957-1958; 389
  - E/ECE/SR. 12/13-27 TWELFTH SESSION., 1958; 389
  - E/ECE/SR. 13/1 -21 THIRTEENTH SESSION., 1958; 389
  - COMMITTEE ON THE DEVELOPMENT OF TRADE, TRADE/WP2/1., 1955-1956; 389
  - MONTHLY BULLETING., 1959-1960; 390
  - EP/WP3/WORKING PAPER no. 30-40., 1960; 390
  - Coal/P/WORKING PAPER no.1-5., 1958; 390
  - STEEL/WORKING PAPER no.215-224., 1960; 390
  - EP/WORKING PAPER no. 182-206., 1960; 390
  - COMMITTEE ON THE DEVELOPMENT OF TRADE., AD HOC WORKING GROUP ON ARBITRATION TRADE/WP1/1-7.; 1955; 391
  - AD HOC WORKING GROUP ON ARBITRATION TRADE/WP1/8-14., 1956; 391
  - AD HOC WORKING GROUP ON ARBITRATION TRADE/WP1/15/Rev. 1., 1958; 391
  - AD HOC WORKING GROUP ON ARBITRATION TRADE/WP1/16-28., 1957-1958; 391
  - TIN CONFERENCE E/Conf. 12/C1., 1950; 392
  - TIN CONFERENCE E/Conf. 12/EX., 1950; 392
  - TIN CONFERENCE E/Conf. 12/BUR., 1950; 392
  - TIN CONFERENCE E/Conf. 12., 1950; 392
  - ECONOMIC ADVISERS CONFERENCE 1 -22., 1961; 393
  - ECONOMIC ADVISERS CONFERENCE 1 -24., 1962; 393
  - ST/ECE/EP 1-6., 393
  - TRADE/WP.4/15-22corr1., 1962; 394
  - E/ECE/426-467., 1962; 394
  - ECONOMIC BULLETIN FOR EUROPE Vol. XVI. no. 1., 1963; 395
  - TRADE 131-151., 1962-1963; 395
  - TRADE 35-68., 1959-1963; 395
  - TRADE/WP3/1-12., 1959-1961; 395
  - TRADE/SM/1-26., 1959; 396
  - TRADE/51-79., 1956-1958; 396
  - E/ECE/TRADE/7-34., 1954-1958; 396
  - TRADE/WP4/1-14 add. 1., 1960-1961; 396
  - E/ECE/SR15/1-27., 1960-1961; 396
  - E/ECE/SR 14/1-24., 1960; 397
  - TRADE/80-89., 1959; 397
  - TRADE/89-110., 1959-1960; 397
  - TRADE/111-130., 1961; 397
  - E/ECE/468-505., 1963; 398
  - E/ECE/397 -428., 1961; 398
  - E/ECE/311-394., 1958-1960'; 398
  - STEEL WORKING PAPER 268/Add. 9-285., 1964; 399
  - STEEL WORKING PAPER 286-299., 1964-1965; 399
  - STEEL 111-114., 1962-1964; 400
  - STEEL/WP4/WORKING PAPER 1- add. 8., 1964; 400
  - ST/ECE/EP/22-26., 1963; 400
  - COAL/147-172., 1961-1964; 400
  - TRANS/283-311., 1964-1966; 401
  - TRANS/SC/180-196., 1964-1965; 401
  - TRANS/SC1/238/REV2-284., 1965-1966; 401
  - W/TRANS/SC2/180-198., 1962-1965; 402
  - TRANS/SC2/102-306., 1962-1964; 402
  - W/TRANS/WP6/190/202., 1965; 402
  - W/TRANS/WP15/100/REV1-124., 1965; 402
  - W/TRANS/WP29/162-193., 1965; 403
  - TRANS/WP29/60-71., 1964-1965; 403
  - CONF/EURSTATS/WG9/35add/6., CONF/EURSTATS/WG9/48.; 1963-1965; 403
  - CONF/EURSTATS/WG4/12., CONF/EURSTATS/WG4/16.; 1964-1965; 403
  - CONF/EURSTATS/WG/197-229., 1963-1965; 403
  - CONF/EURSTATS/WG13/24-32., 1963-1964; 404
  - CONF/EURSTATS/WG19/1-17., 1964; 404
  - CONF/EURSTATS/WG20/2-4., 1964; 404
  - CONF/EURSTATS/WG20/1-2., 1963-1964; 404
  - CONF/EURSTATS/WG21/3add/1-6., 1964; 404
  - CONF/EURSTATS/WG21/1-7., 1965; 404
  - CONF/EURSTATS/WG23/1-10., 1965; 404
  - ST/ECE/HOU/13-15., 1964-1965; 405
  - GAS/WORKING PAPER/115-162., 1965-1966; 405
  - ST/ECE/EP/23-33., 1964-1965; 406
  - ST/ECE/GAS., 1963-1964; 406
  - HOU/WORKING PAPER/173., 1964; 407
  - HOU/WORKING PAPER/183., 1965; 407
  - COAL/CTSC/WORKING PAPER/NO.154 add 2-169., 1965; 408
  - COAL/P/WORKING PAPER/86-101., 1965; 408
  - COAL/U/WORKING PAPER/13-26., 1964-1965; 408
  - ARGI/WP1/330., 1964; 409
  - ARGI/WP1/405., 1965; 409
  - EP/WORKING PAPER/280/310., 1964-1965; 410
  - EP/WP3/WORKING PAPER/57-90., 1964-1965; 410
  - STEEL/WORKING PAPER/300-312 REV.1., 1965; 410
  - STEEL/WP4/WORKING PAPER/2-3 add 8., 1965; 410
  - MONTHLY COAL STATISTICAL SUMMARY/187-198., 1964; 411
  - EP/WP7/WORKING PAPER/3 add. 3-9 add. 5., 1964-1965; 411
  - TRADE/WP1/23-54., 1963; 411
  - EP/157-165., 1965; 411
  - TIM/SAW/1-34., 1964; 412
  - TRANS/WP6/82-95., 1962-1965; 412
  - W/TRANS/WP30/74-87., 1964-1965; 413
  - TRANS/WP30/93-98., 1964-1965; 413
  - W/TRANS/WP30/169-195., 1964-1965; 413
  - W/TRANS/WP34/7 REV.-39., 1963-1965; 413
  - W/TRANS/SC/3/37Add.Rev. 1-77., 1964-1965; 413
  - TRANS/SC/3/34-49., 1963-1965; 414
  - W/TRANS/238REV.8-337., 1964-1965; 414
  - E/ECE/16SR/1-29., 1961; 415
  - E/ECE/SR17/1-27., 1962-1963; 415
  - E/ECE/SR18/1-25., 1964; 415
  - E/ECE/SR19/1-24., 1965; 416
  - E/ECE/SR20/1-24., 1965; 416
  - E/ECE/DOCS/2-20., 1959-1960; 417
  - E/ECE/DOCS/42-56., 1963; 417
  - E/ECE/DOCS/57-75., 1964-1965; 417
  - TRADE/152-187., 1964; 418
  - E/WATER POLL./SEM. 4-5., 1962-1963; 418
  - HOU. ELKDERIJ COLL./A1-B2 ADD1., 1965; 418
- UN/ECONOMIC COMMISSION FOR ASIA AND THE FAR EAST (ECAFE).
  In 1947 ingestelde economische regionale commissie van de Verenigde Naties, ter vergroting van de economische activiteiten en stimulering van de economische betrekkingen van de landen binne de regio de buitenwereld.
  - Economie Commission on for Asia and The Far East., 1951-1953; 716
    Committee on Industry and Trade (Subcommittee on Electric Power Committee on Industry and Trade (Summery records) Lignite Experts
    Working Party on small-scala industrie and handicraft, marketing
  - Economie Commission on for Asia and The Far East., 1950-1954; 717
    Committee on Industry and Trade (Working Party on Financial Aspects of economie developrnent)
    Committee on Industry and Trade (Subcommittee on Iron and Steel inland transport (Summery records)
  - Economie Commission on for Asia and The Far East., 1951-1952; 718
    Committee on Industry and Trade (Working Party of experts on mobilization of demostic capital
  - Economie Commission on for Asia and The Far East., 1951-1955; 719
    E/CN 11/1-322
  - Economie Commission on for Asia and The Far East., 1952-1955; 720
    E/CN 11/323-408
  - Economie Commission on for Asia and The Far East., 1950-1951; 721
    Committee on Industry and Trade E/CN 11/1 en T 14-40
  - Economie Commission on for Asia and The Far East., 1950-1954; 722
    E/CN 11/1 en T 42-76
  - Economie Commission on for Asia and The Far East., 1950-1956; 723
    ST/ECAFE/SER.H
- INTERNATIONAL MATERIALS CONFERENCE.
  - International Tin Conference en International Tin Study Group., 1945-1949; 2294
    669.6(100)
  - International Materials Conference Zwavel Committee., 1951; 621
    Documenten 1-84
  - Diverse Stukken., 622
    - International Materials Conference Zwavel Committee, 1952-1953
      Documenten 103-193
    - International Materials Conference Zwavel Committee, 1951-1952
      o.a. W.P.-stukken no. 6-67. Pressreleases e.d.
  - Diverse Stukken., 623
    - International Materials Conference Zwavel Committee, 1952-1953
      W.P.-stukken no. 82-119
    - International Materials Conference Pulp-Papier Committee, 1951-1952
      o.a. Documenten no. 1-88, W.P.-stukken no. 5-55 en Pressreleases
  - Diverse Stukken., 624
    - International Materials Conference Wool Committee, 1951-1952
      Documenten no. 1-103
    - International Materials Conference Wool Committee, 1952
      Stat. tabellen
  - Rubber study group and rubber news., 1953; 819
  - The International Tin Study Group., 820
  - Rubber Conferentie te Rome., 1953; 1025
- VREDESCONFERENTIE VAN PARIJS, 1946
  - Conferentie Parijs., 1946; 2281
    Verslagen diverse Commissies
  - Conferentie Parijs., 1946; 2282